{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"7131/27",
			"answer":"7131/27",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4862/59",
			"answer":"4862/59",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3219/74",
			"answer":"3219/74",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4698/76",
			"answer":"4698/76",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1337/70",
			"answer":"1337/70",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"42.77/4.4",
			"answer":"42.77/4.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.3036/30",
			"answer":"0.3036/30",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"70.95/0.011",
			"answer":"70.95/0.011",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.315/8.9",
			"answer":"5.315/8.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"92.57/6.8",
			"answer":"92.57/6.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}